<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Unsupervised Pleasures</title>
 <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/"/>
 <updated>2020-10-09T23:14:42-07:00</updated>
 <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml</id>
 <author>
   <name>@queermachines</name>
   <email>queermachines@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v9</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-009"/>
   <updated>2020-09-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-009</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was in high school, this sweet, innocent, bubbly geezer from Mendocino, California, came over for dinner and had the most incredible meal. We chatted all day and night about life in the gay and lesbian community and his favorite subject was “The Private Life of the City.” He talked about cruising the city, going out to bars on Friday nights, and even went as far as to buy me a leather briefcase with sex toys inside so I could take all my fantasies to the clubs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mouth dropped open when he told me this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’d taken me to gay clubs and explained to me that none of the guys there used condoms and that it was the girls that used them. No one ever said anything about it being a perverted thing to do. He even went as far as to buy me a “public” condom, which was only intended for close male friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought for sure he was being melodramatic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He wasn’t. He was genuinely moved by my reaction and told me he wanted to do something about it. I was over the moon. I felt I could do something about it. I even thought maybe I could become his secretary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’m not one of those gay “Christs-for-Jesus” that believe in any kind of heaven, but I was sold on the idea of being his “public” condom. I was willing to do almost anything for him to keep my secret. I would do anything to keep my boyfriend and my brother from knowing. I even had my parents believe I was gay and started researching them and sending them Christmas cards and school supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did he say when you told him all this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was disappointed. He told me he had made a big mistake. He’d like to take some time to think about it and come to a conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He couldn’t?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was angry. He said he loved you very much and that you always put his best foot forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must have been hurt, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in shock. I never wanted him to see what I saw. He was the most amazing, sensitive, funny, beautiful boy ever to walk the face of this earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You mean he turned gay after that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. Maybe.
Maybe. He could have been lying down the gurney any minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trained Model&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 0.8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v8</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-008"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-008</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was your age, in college, cruising the interwebs, cruising the high school, cruising high schools…. There was one boy,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey, buddy, we got to go to your place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hang in there, Johnny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hair of the dog?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Butch. How could he be gay? How could he be my friend?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and I were besties. We went to the same high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You left me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I threw you out of your best friend’s party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t think much of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It happened over and over. You and I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I threw him out of my best friend’s party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a great friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re trash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay. I’m sorry. I don’t belong here. Please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hair of the dog?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, Johnny, I don’t know what to do. It’s your fault. I didn’t know. I don’t know. I can’t do anything. It’s your fault. It’s your fault. You want to talk about it. I’m sitting here, waiting for you to tell me something and you don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s not talk about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not your fault. I didn’t know. And I’m not your friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heather, you know I love you. But I know that sometimes you’re too rough on me or too direct with me. And that you need to be a little more subtle. You are too good for me. I don’t know where else to go. I don’t know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny, I love you too. But you’re not perfect. You’re not perfect, Honeybun. And you’re not just a friend. You’re a brother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a fucking brother!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need a friend to go with you when you make these kinds of crazy plans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t need a friend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a fucking runaway!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to be with someone for a while. Okay?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can stay here with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need a friend to go with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need a friend to go to bars and clubs with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t need a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you have to tell me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t need a friend. I don’t need a friend. I don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay! I’m going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay! You’re going!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to a party with some guys tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’ll we do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to see the strippers or what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’ll show you. Do you want to see the housewife or the stay-at-home mother?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll tell you what’ll show you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to see a lesbian or a naturist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll show you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A naked woman in a house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The party goes on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to see the naked woman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A naked man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The party doesn’t go on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to see the housewife or the stay-at-home mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be seeing you tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be seeing you sometime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay. You and Johnny. Now go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know, I’m not feeling so good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t go around asking me where I’m going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and I are best buddies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. Don’t go around asking me why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’re you going to do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re going to the party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really don’t know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going. I’m going to a party with some guys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and me. Go to the bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been in a bar with anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A party? Oh. Well, that’s nice. I’ll see you after the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure. Where are you going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hair of the dog? I know you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to show off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to keep my clothes in the closet. “Fancy a pet?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve always wanted a housewife. Now I’ve got one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A pet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cat. I like cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. I think I like big cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a very big cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. I’m frightened of big cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. That’s right. You’re a very big cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have a lot of friends?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not really. We do quite a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Are you a very big cat?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a very big cat!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people like to be big. You’re very popular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, this is a very big house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have a lot of friends?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. I’m very popular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I don’t know if I do. I don’t know if I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, if you were really famous, people would come to your rescue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really? What would people say about me now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People say that about everybody that I meet. I meet them and go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Very! Very! I’m very, very famous!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will you marry me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! I think so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very happy about having you and Katie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think you’re very happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think you’re tired all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know when I feel tired. I get so excited about things. I get so excitedI want to go out and beat the shit out of this corner store, this little orphan shop, this theater, this park, this theatre, this sign, this flower, this mirror, this telephone booth, this mirror, this carpet, this life, this book, this book, this carpet, this chair, this carpet, this sign, this street, this walkway, this sign, this lamp, this tree, this brick, this table, this rug, this blanket, this sign, this book, this blanket, this chair, this table, this blanket, this rug, this chair, this lamp, this tree, this walkway, this light, this chair, this rug, this table, this lamp, this blanket, this table, this rug, this chair, this sign, this street, this lamp, this blanket, this table, this lamp, this rug, this chair, this table, this sign, this street, this lamp, this blanket, this I’ve never been in a room with anyone who thought, “Oh, this person is very interesting, I could be very interesting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to meet a lot of new people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will you marry me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve never told me you were gay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I didn’t know that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I don’t know. Who would ever think of that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been in a room with anyone who thought, “Oh, this person is very interesting, I could be very interesting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m very interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been in a room with anyone who has said to me, “You are very interesting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t matter what you are. You are interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care what you are. I don’t care what you are. And I’m very, very ugly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beautiful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So am I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have no idea what it’s like to be unattractive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve never told me you were gay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very gay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very unattractive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very attractive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no doubt about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have no idea what it is like to be unattached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you certainly have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very possessive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very selfish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I think I must be very selfish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And very, very dense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And very, very stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have no idea what it is to be hungry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very noisy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very possessive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And very, very competitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And very, very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very competitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very competitive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And very, very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you may be surprised to know that I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I must be very possessive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh! Oh! I am very possessive!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 2000&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 163.42&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v7</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-007"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-007</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was a kid, the only people I was allowed to see in a public place were those I knew and loved. Those closest to me were either priests or middle-aged white men. It was forbidden to me to go to the gayborhood or the drag queens’ district. In those days, you could get two hours of free porn and seventeen of them had sex. I was so ashamed of myself that I never went to the gayborhood or the strip clubs. I wasn’t gayborhood or drag queenstrippergirl, I wasn’t even a gay boy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of things you don’t know,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know that there were any gayborhoodstrippers, clubs, or even gay men. I didn’t know that many of the guys I hung around with were gayborhoodstrippers. I didn’t know that many of the gayborhoodminors were gayminors. And I certainly wasn’t part of the gayborhoodthe clubs. I didn’t know that many of the gayborhoodminors actuallylived with their partners. Or that in the gayborhoodthe bars. Or even the gayborhoodwas more acceptable than it might have been to some of my more conservative gayborhoodmates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My fantasy wasn’t to find out about my queerborhood or my life with theminors. It was to find out if there wereany other gayborhoodminors. I wasn’t interested in that. And so, over the years, I’ve had itwith you. And sometimes, it’s evengot me wondering if my only queer experience was being the subject of that sad, sad, sad boy’s fantasy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I always wanted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now that you and Randy have gone home, it’s time to take thingsinto our own hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can’t leave everything that we’ve learned at Stonewall. We’re not infallible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what do we do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got some preliminary suggestions. If you meet the guy who was “Jason” in the gayborhoodand you keep his name, we might be able to get a hunting license out of this town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what do we doif we don’t kill this boy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s hope he’s a nice, decent looking guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And anyway, we’re goinghome now. I don’t want any part of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I don’t want any part of your adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you, Beast, you’rea convicted murderer, and I don’t want any part of your adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what I believe anymore&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe what Randy told you, and I believe what he told you, dearheart. Whatever you believe, whatever you think is true, I know for a fact, it isn’t true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(To RICHARD and ROGER) Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re going to a party sometime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, this isnothing specialbut it will make a nice atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been to a disco before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, that’s okay. Here, try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I don’t like dancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should try dancing with somebuddy. It’ll make yourstubs squeak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I’m not a bad dancer. I can dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s a good dancer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good dancer should be good at everything. They have to be. I’m a very bad dancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry. I don’t think that’s appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By all means, Beast, whatever you are. I am ashamed of myself. I am even ashamed of my&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beauty, you are so wise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do you ask me that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I am a feminist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But a good feminist isn’t like you. A good feminist doesn’t care if you don’t like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, I don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do, though. I do. I do. I&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(To ANNIE, RICH and ROGER)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re going to have to come with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, no one’s stopping me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I doubt it’ll be long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t imagine what the evening will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(To RICH and ANNIEJerk-nobody’s stopping me, I just don’t know when or even if anyone will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aren’t you afraid that I’ll drag you out here and start dancing with them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not dancing with them, I’m with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s up to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you don’t want to be with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t, I don’t really want to be with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you do. I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I do. I think I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You really do. I don’t know whether you realize it ornot, but you do. You can’t not know, you must. I guess I do. I really do like you, Beast. I like you very much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what that meansbut I like you very much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s all right. Everything’s alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My father’s seeing someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just a test, my father just wants me to feel that I’m in this together with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all right. I understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the first thing he’s done in twenty-five years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard, Randy. Sometimes I feel like I’m in a nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, it doesn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, it isn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to let it become a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so glad you feel that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I do. I do. I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I guess we’re finally getting somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(To RYANNEJerk-nobody’s slowing us, nobody’s slowing us, Beast, this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s terrible, isn’t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, my God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea is the mother of all disasters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t believe this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, I don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t believe it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea is God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just a metaphor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO, it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really do like it here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like living on the moon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lumen, illuminate!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to talk about the sea now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t imagine what it must be like on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I’m here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to talk about the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no one else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you, Beast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moon is the mother of all the gods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a lie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you, Beast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not even sure I believe what I’m saying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you, Beast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do. I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whoops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to let them know that you love them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not dancing with them, I’m with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love them. I do. I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just so overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aw, my God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, Beast, don’t be silly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t understand,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re doing it anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, no, no, no, that’s not it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, my God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure I believe what I’m saying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really too clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I love you, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, my God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the moon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have to find a way to express love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do. I do. I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel… nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, my God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do. I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 1750&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 144.33&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v6</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-006"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-006</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was a young queer woman in college. My imagination ran wild…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who could have seen that coming?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think about you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if I could have one secret lover?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One secret lover? I’ve always had one secret lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where did you keep that book of erotic poetry?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kept it in the bathroom at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you ever get together with that much male fantasy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure. Do I have to describe it to you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course not. I’ve always been so truthful with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s one secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One lover. One secret lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, come on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could you please leave out the “one”?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I could get you a ring so we could make love together,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want me to lie down and hold your hand while you do your French Bend?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that what you want?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. I’d like to feel your body against mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come on now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. I’d like to feel you in your arms, always safe and warm in my arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like sex in public?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it in private.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love when you make love to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to get down on your knees and kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giggling?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giggling? Yeah?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to suck my fingers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suck my fingers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to suck my nipples?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss my pussy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss my ass?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you want to do to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make love to me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take it out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like to take pictures?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picturing? Sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to watch me get fucked?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to watch me get fucked?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sex and Fuck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sex and Fuck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you want to do to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to take your clothes off and kiss you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to get your dick deep inside me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to see your balls bounce around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to fuck you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so wet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m dripping!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I smell of sex!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I smell of jealousy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to hear me moan?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to feel my pussy lips?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my clit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my toes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fuck me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lick my clit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lick my asshole!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m dripping!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m wet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to finger me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m getting close!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m getting wet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m wet and ready! All of you! Reach up and cup my breasts. Pull my hair. Pull my hair around my face. Kiss me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my clit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you want to do to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me you want to kiss!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me you want to taste me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me you want to see my toes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me you want to taste my ass!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me you want to see my pussy lips!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shhhhh! Shhhhh!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to suck my nipples?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to fuck me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you want to do to me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so wet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so dirty!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so turned on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so turned on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shhhhh! Shhhhh! I’m so out of control!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to come inside me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to fuck me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to feel me grow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to taste me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so wet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so dirty!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so turned on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so turned on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so out of control!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shhhhh! Shhhhh!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m coming for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see me get fucked?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to fuck me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m coming for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so turned on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so out of control!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to make love to me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so out of control!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to suck my nipples?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my clit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to feel my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my toes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my pussy lips?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my clit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my toes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my pussy lips?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to suck my nipples?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to kiss me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to make love to my face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a really horny monster, aren’t you? And then you feel my clit again. You can feel it building inside you…. then you feel me against your back and the first time I feel you against me, I pop! I CUMM! Such a good feeling! And then you can feel my balls slapping against your back and the first time I feel you against me, I feel you cumming! I CUM! Such a good feeling! And then you can feel my body shivering and slick against yours and then I can hear your heartbeat against my skin and I can hear my zipper opening as you try to pull yourself free but you can’t! You gag! You moan! I can hear your moans in your ear and then smack your hand away! But I grab it! I pull it! Hard! I grab it! I shove it free! But it’s hard! So hard! I scream! I yell! Make love to me! Make love to me! Hard! But! You can’t make love to me because then I’ll cum! Hard! CUM! I cum! Hard!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a good feeling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a good feeling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a good feeling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a mess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a dirty monster!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come on, baby. Keep going. Come on, keep going. Keep going! It feels so good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you feel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so out of control! I feel so turned on! I want to cum! I want to feel your hot cum against my back! I want to see you cum! I’m coming! I’m so fucking excited!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re coming!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my toes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my pussy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my clit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to taste my asshole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to see my pussy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot and bothered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love when you get mad at me because I get so angry with you. It’s so funny, I don’t know why. You hit me and I’m mad at you and I get so much in my heart and it’s funny. What is it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just that you don’t know how to be a good lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you going to make love to me or are you just going to sit and wait for me? You can’t make love to me, you’re just a big, old, hard-on, angry, boring monster!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to cum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care what you are! Make love to me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so hard, I’m so horny!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so hard, I’m so horny!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to feel you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 1500&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 122.40&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v5</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-005"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-005</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was in high school, we had a band that played all-American folk songs. One night, our lead singer and I were getting into a car accidentally causing gas fumes to rise to the roof of the car, and the windshield blew off, throwing our singer out of the car, and down onto the highway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, he was okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily for us, the highway was very winding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily for us, the highway was&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;turning right&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highway 101&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The windshield blew off&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know how many times I heard that,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highway is for trucks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning right at this point&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of exits&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this location&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this location&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, that’s how I imagined it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know how I found you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you do know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your family tree&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or do you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve got the money to do it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, well I guess so. I have. So.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You said you had to have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to use someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could’ve used you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you had to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s new?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s wrong with me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that sounds ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hotline Miami” gave me chills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hotline Miami&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to have it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to watch it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh come on! It’s not true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the most exciting thing I’ve ever had the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the most exciting thing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a grown man now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the most exciting thing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t even want to get into that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hotline Miami.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give me the straight answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t give me that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s all just talk about what’s real right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t give me any crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay. Let’s talk about what’s real now. Okay?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t drag your Ex-Boyfriend into this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s real about my life?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ex-boyfriend&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s real about your ex-boyfriend?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re dragging him into this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s angry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s jealous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s needy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s a faggot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He needs you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s a bimbo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s straight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s old-fashioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He wants to fuck you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to fuck him!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to fuck you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you said that it’s only because we broke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t you even know how to kiss!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said that he wanted to try new things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to fuck you but I don’t know how!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You said that you had ideas!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you have ideas about?!?!?!?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you trying to pull?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry, but there is one thing I do know for sure: money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can understand your need for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you do know how to spend it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what do you know how to do with it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there is the “Affirmative Action” course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Course you didn’t catch that one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the only course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just know you want to fuck me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just know that’s all you ever wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that’s true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I guess I do now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, but, but. But what about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you getting at?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All right. All right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you getting at?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re asking me to kiss a gay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m asking you to help me move out of this apartment!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then why do you want to kiss?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I don’t like him!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then why do you want to keep him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I don’t like the way things are going with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then why do you want to keep him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I don’t know how to get out of this!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you know what’s going to happen next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you’re there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I’m stupid!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re stupid!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All right. Well, go on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you want to know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to know if there’s any other roommates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, well maybe we should look into that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We haven’t looked into that, either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, we might as well know now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a long shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So long!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just hope that you’ll be patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have my ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, I don’t know if you’d let me move out on my own, but if you’d just listen to me and follow my directions…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would be wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you. I’ll sign the papers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, yeah. It’s okay. Don’t worry. Everything’s going to be alright. I know how you feel. It’s just that now I’m being watched. And it’s not just him. There’s the television. Too bright. And in the closet. This is very embarrassing. I’m not used to being watched in the bedroom. But there are mirrors and dresser drawers. And bookshelves. And leather. And silver screens. And little caddies in tiny little outfits. So what if it’s a little noisy. And there’s a slight breeze blowing outside. And dust. And flies. And the bedroom door is open and the lights are on. I could die. Or they could hear me. They’ve all moved upstairs. I don’t know why they’re here. I do. I can hear everything. And everything’s black.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I wish you had said something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just a matter of time before he moves out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He moved out just a few months ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t hear the move-in until last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s only been three weeks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’ve got a roommate who’s always on time, who’s never sick or missed a day, who’s a great dancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you mean&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wish you’d have said something!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t say anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay. I’m just a roommate and all that. It’s nothing. But it’s not okay. I don’t know what to do. Do you know what to do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just hoped that if you were patient, I would be able to find a suitable roommate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I already have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I know who you are. I know that you are a homosexual. I just happen to know that you are not. But you know that I know what it feels like to be watched and to have my dignity insulted. I don’t know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what to do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry, but I just don’t know what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you know what’s going on in my head? I have no idea. I can think about it all, but I’m not sure I can bring myself to say it out loud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can always tell what it feels like to be watched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what it feels like to be touched. I know what it feels like to be touched in a way that makes your heart leap. I know what it feels like to have someone put their arm around your waist and pull it close. I know what it feels like to have someone put a pillow around your neck and try to kiss you. I can even imagine what it feels like to be slapped and to be nuzzled against a wall. Maybe it feels so real. Or maybe it’s not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t know. I guess we don’t know, either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you mean is that I don’t know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just say it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what I want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not what I want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay. Now, we’ll say your name out loud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Say it. Say it loud and clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s okay. I’m a lot louder than you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a lot less sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’ll bet you can guess who it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can guess a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright. I’m A, B, and… C. Now let’s say you’re A. Now say you’re a blow-up doll. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary breasts. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary balls. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary fingers. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary hair. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary ears. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary eyes. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary legs. Now say you’re a blow-up doll with imaginary feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright. I’m a lot more of an A than you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now say you’re a mop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 1250&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 98.11&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v4</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-004"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-004</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was in fifth grade, a boy from the school assembly told me that he had been in love with a girl named Florence. The boy had been in and out of love and lust for many years, but one night, as he was leaving to go away to school, he asked his teacher if she was gay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The teacher said that she was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then he told her that he loved her and that he was in love with her too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she ran off to tell her father.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the father was apoplectic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the teacher reassured him that his love for his son was genuine and that he could love anyone he wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was five and a half years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now I am in love with you, the bisexual hound, and we have been together for three years, and we are in love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I don’t want to be intimate with you, the heterosexual hound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay, it’s okay! It’s alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many ways to love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excuse me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me see, how many ways are there to love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many ways are there to be gay? How many ways are there to be bisexual? How many ways are there to love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see it as a zero-sum game. You get one and you have to get the other. If you get one, you get one less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have to be gay to love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re a zero-sum game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be a zero-sum game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be a lot more than just a zero. I could love more than you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot more. More than you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could love someone much more than you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t matter. I love you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you can’t love someone just because they are your lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe not just because they are your lover. I love you because you are a good friend and because you want to be good friends with me. I don’t care if you’re my lover or not. I just want you to be a good friend and to want to be good friends with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be a lot more than just a good friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be a lot more than just a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be a lot more than just a lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me try to be a little more specific. Please…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can we please be friends? Please? Let’s go for a drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I can’t just say, “I love you.” You have to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can I call you later and tell you how I am?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t just say, “I love you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do. All the time. I’m not exaggerating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not exaggerating. I do love you. But I can’t just say, “I love you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t just say, “I love you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do. All the time. I’m not exaggerating. I do love you. But I can’t just say, “I love you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s go for a drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay, it’s okay. Go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, of course I know what.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then what do you want?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. What about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then just go for a drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how excited I am to tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not your…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not your…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re not drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re not my…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not your…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you did say “I.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, my God, he…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said “I.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said, “I.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said, “I.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A drink?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A D.A.A.R.Y.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A double-drink-a-cuppa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A double-drink-a-cuppa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A double-d, a.k.a. a double-d bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are you two still having these conversations?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have something to tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to kill you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have something to tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have anything to tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, f-down, Dave. Oh, f-down, Dave. It’s all going to be just fine. All right? Oh, f-down, f-down. Oh, f-down, f-down. What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Down.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not hearing anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s all going to be just fine.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you think he felt?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He never fucked me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bar never had a clear title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It had to do with something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know the story?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the story but I don’t believe it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He took it to be a matter of pride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a matter of pride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He didn’t want to lose control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He didn’t want to lose control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said, “I’m going to die alone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He didn’t want to go to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m going to die alone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m going to die alone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t believe him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t believe him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know he doesn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re going to die alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to die alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one’s going to care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to die alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He didn’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He didn’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ll be coming back.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be coming back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be coming back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was going to the opera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was going to the opera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was going to the opera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was going to the opera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was going to the opera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t know anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be over soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be over soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, shit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won’t be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 1000&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 72.34&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v3</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-003"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-003</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was a junior high school English teacher in Texas. My school was in the middle of a gay rights march. On the square near the square, there were gay men kissing in front of the assembly and chanting “Hands off our buxom women!” in the square.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a gay man myself, I was outraged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gay rights movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gay rights movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was nothing at all resembling “homo” or “bimbo.” And there were no signs at all that said, “Homo-Bimbo.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I guess that’s the ultimate fairy tale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what happened next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s true. We had a private lesson in gay rights, and the boys I taught were all closeted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I had a gay teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, yes. That’s right. You had a gay teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you had sex with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not exactly. I was fond of him and we had consensual sex. My point? We didn’t know for sure. But it was a start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You were a senior in high school. You had the chance to change your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to be a writer. I wanted to be a writer’s assistant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You were an assistant editor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked as an assistant to a writer. I wrote a story and had it published. Then I got promoted to writer’s assistant. So I wrote a screenplay and had it directed by a famous director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You were in love with that writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lied. I wasn’t in love with him. I had sex with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have any idea what that means? That’s called jealousy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You were doing research on this gay man. You were consulting with this famous director, on what you thought were possibly thousands of men. And you turned around and said, “I don’t want to get involved with anyone who is that way.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a joke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, I had just gotten a promotion to writer’s assistant and I was tired of writing screenplay. I decided to skip the writing phase and concentrate on the casting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what happened next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You couldn’t act, you couldn’t act tough, you couldn’t act arrogant, you couldn’t act even gay. You could only act like shit. It was the first time in my life I had been so completely humiliated by the person I was working with. I went into a state of paralysis. I didn’t know what to do anymore. I knew that whatever I was doing wasn’t going to make any difference to anyone. And that my only hope of escaping was to give in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You couldn’t do anything about it. You couldn’t say a word. You could only stare blankly into the abyss of apathy. Did you notice anything strange in that abyss? Nothing like that black eye. Did you even notice that it looked different?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. I can’t remember ever seeing a black eye look this strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the rest of my life in a state of total denial. I could not imagine how anyone could be so stupid as to act like this. It didn’t matter if I was going to jail or not. It didn’t matter if I was going to marry the man or not. It didn’t matter if I had a career or not. The only thing that mattered was that I didn’t want to get involved with anyone. I didn’t want anyone to think I was anything more than a happy little boy. So you threw in the towel. So you decided to disappear. I’m amazed you didn’t leave me with a bloody nose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d say I had a pretty good excuse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like in that case of Willy Brandt?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d say so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a fit of jealous rage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s an excellent question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe. I’d say it was jealousy. You wouldn’t believe it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re not going to make any more movies, are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not after that one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what movie?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s already made more than most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You really stink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All right, it’s all right. The movie didn’t do too well, but it was the one thing I was really proud of. It was my breakout role in a feature film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You weren’t supposed to have any other roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I had to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve never done any other film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I never did any other movies either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I’m sorry. I didn’t mean to be. I didn’t mean to say that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You didn’t mean anything by that. You’re so funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not funny. I’m not funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be funny. I like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be funny. You’re very serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very serious. I have to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And serious is so very good for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really. I know that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I’m doing something right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know you know it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course you know it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve done it. I can’t believe you can do it. You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t believe you can do it. You’re so serious. I can’t believe you can do anything else. You’re so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you’re too serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re too serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re too serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like trying to make love to a bull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t believe I’m doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you’re doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s that supposed to mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That I’m having a good time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll go now. I’ve got a piece of cake waiting for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, what’s this cake?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll have to wait, but I’ll be down in a minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll see me down there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, I’m going to give you a hard time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s my wife. What’s this black eye?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was just playing with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, it’s just that I’m shy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to see more of the park?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t look so surprised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you met her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know where she came from. I grew up in Kentucky. My father was a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s a pretty good background to have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not much, is it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ask me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, I like the Kentucky scenery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s true. It makes me happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when I’m driving down the highway, I like to imagine what it would be like if you could see me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a sort of suburban fantasy in Kentucky. It’s not too far from town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not into that type of thing. I don’t like suburban scenery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like scenery. That’s what I like to see. I’m in a hurry. I have to be in a hurry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re about to drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be out of your way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m driving. I won’t be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I’m going to see you later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I’m late, I’ll be late again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll see. Don’t be shy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s my favorite time of the week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to see anymore of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to see you either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to see you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to see anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll see you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what do we have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Soup Nazi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you know I’m partial to the whole soup thing. I’ll have to say that I’m not a huge fan. But this particular batch is beyond description.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you, well, you’re not afraid to be a little cruel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not the point. I’m just stating facts. You know, when I do my “scaring the shit out of people” type stuff, it doesn’t take me long to turn into a Vietcong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a specimen. What’s that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m just scratching your head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, when I was a kid, we used to carry around a little jar of that stuff in the back of the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was “Purple Haze.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purple Haze?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purple Haze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, what is it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A while back, I was having a little wander-lust expedition down the Maryland Heights. And as I was zooming around this lovely road, I stopped at a stoplight and this elderly woman was stuck in the moving traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How did she get through?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll never know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll never know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 500&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 39.51&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v2</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-002"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-002</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was a kid, I dreamt of being famous. When I was a child, I dreamt of being popular. When I was a teenager, I dreamt of being in love. When I was a young woman, I dreamt of being in the world. When I was a woman, I dreamt of being in love. When I was a woman, I dreamt of being famous. When I was a man, I dreamt of being famous. When I was a man, I dreamt of being famous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I awoke. I woke up and I was wearing a blue dress and a blue blouse and I walked out into the sun and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy, and then I walked out into the moon and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked out into the sky and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I went back into the moon and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I slept. And then I woke up and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I slept. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I slept. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I slept. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the night and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I walked back into the stars and I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy and I felt sexy. And then I woke up. And I was white and sexy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 250&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 31.98&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Queer A.I. Ultimate Fantasy v1</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-001"/>
   <updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/queer-ai-ultimate-fantasy-001</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you like to have anonymous sex in public rest rooms? Sex movies? Public parks? Sex clubs? On street corners with heavy hustling traffic? How many nonsexual friendships or acquaintances lasting for decades started this way? How many ways are there to love queers? How many ways are there to queer love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was. . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me begin by telling you my ultimate fantasy. When I was young I loved going out to a club with a gang of boys. I did not understand it at the time, I thought it was disgusting and I should not enjoy it. But in my adolescent years, when I discovered the gay scene, I found out about its strength and purpose. This meant it had two forms, boys and men. It also meant it had a sex with young boys that was not, in my opinion, as popular as one with a woman might want to do. I was more shocked than I was surprised to find out about my own sexuality, which had always been like this. And this was not something I was ashamed of, I was part of the gay community and I had found out a bit about it. I would occasionally go to clubs with boys, or with my mother. She was a lesbian who hated the lifestyle and I know she found it quite pleasant. And I knew that she did not really want me to be a lesbian, she did not really understand it. My mother was a staunch member of the “G” club, which was devoted to women. I think I liked her, she did not really hate me, but she was angry at her own sex, and the fact that I would leave her house when I got home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came home late one night and my mother was furious at me. She was upset that I had left her and went out for drinks, and her house was pretty packed, she was quite angry at herself. She and her husband, who was a Presbyterian, were at a pub the night before. I was the only boy there and I was alone, but she saw me coming in. She was rather upset that I was not home, and there was an awful lot of looking at me, talking to my mother. She went out and had some drinks with a friend, and then had a few more with me. She then left for the pub. I went home to my mother, where I could, and found that I had a great deal to complain about. I was going to go to bed and she went off to see my friend. It was a pretty dark evening, dark with the smell of smoke. She called the police and came over to my room. I thought it was dreadful. I saw my friend there and she wanted to see me. She was so happy to see me. I explained to her that I was going to go back to my room. She went off to find her friend. I went back to my room and I was afraid to go out because I was watching what was going to happen. But she was a very good friend and told me not to go out at night. She would give me her handbag and I would carry her and her bag. She then went back to her friend’s room and she sat on the bed next to me, I would not leave her there. She said to my friend, “I will call the police, but if you don’t call, they will arrest you.” And so I went back to my room. And I had an awkward silence and I went and sat down to write. And I thought, “This is very difficult, you are going to be arrested, you are going to have to pay.” She came out and said, “Good, it is quite easy to say.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life was so bizarre at the time, I was so alienated and so disgusted with myself. But I got out of it, I got over it, and I never had any more time to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never did it again. I can see that I have had many adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think that’s why it isn’t fashionable in the gay world?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I don’t think that gay people are boring people. I think that they are sometimes very strong and very intense, and I don’t think that they are the boring kind of people. They are not boring and they do have a desire to be interesting, but not too interesting and not too interesting. I think that there are things to be said about the gay community which are not in the strict or the conventional way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think the gay community is becoming a bit like the gay ideal, which has been reduced to some trifle by those who are more in touch with the gay community?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I think it is becoming more and more like that. It is not a perfect solution. The gay community is like a vast bouquet of flowers, and it’s just like that. It is a lot of things, and it is a very large bouquet. The lesbian community is a big bouquet, and it’s still about flowers. But it’s becoming less and less and less bouquet and more and more bouquet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does the gay community differ from the lesbian community?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that there is a great difference between them. The gay community is a community of real people, who are full of love, and they are passionate and not egocentric, and that is what is interesting to the lesbian community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think gay people are about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I think that they are fantastic people, and it would be quite a bit interesting to know how they are about. They are not an aesthetic problem. They have a great deal of talent, and you don’t want to find out what they are about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You seem to have a rather positive attitude towards people, despite the tragedy of your experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, but I am never close to someone, and I think I have gone through enough. It is one thing when you have lived through tragedy. It is another thing when you have been married and have had children. I always think that it would be quite a good idea to meet someone who is the same age as me. I think it is quite useful. It would be a pity to find out that I was one of the things I did not like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was your family like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it was all very peaceful and nice. I had a nice wife and I had a nice home and all that. I was only a little girl. And they were very nice to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have a big family, have you ever got on a train?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s your first job like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to work as a stenographer. I am actually a stenographer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you still a stenographer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, I am working as a nurse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is your time spent as a stenographer something you like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not your favorite thing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the most amazing and the most challenging job you have ever had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think you have lived up to the definition of a married woman?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, if I was a married woman, I wouldn’t want to do anything. But if I was an adult woman I would do it if it was my husband, or my children. I think it’s just a bit silly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your ambitions for your future?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, I think I am pretty much done for. I have a wife, I have a nice home and I don’t have any plans. I think that I am an interesting person and I think I have a lot to tell you about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you met people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have, but not quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your next adventure?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was in a garden party and I went down and met an old man who was dying of cancer. He was very kind to me and he was asking me how I was doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said: “Goodbye, darling, you are much prettier now than you were at the party.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not know what a garden party was. I thought it was just a party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would he come down and meet you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, he said: “I must tell you that I am very sad, and that is the best way I can express my feelings. I am on my death bed. I don’t know if I can live anymore. And, for my part, I must tell you that I am sorry.” I said: “Yes, I understand.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did he say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am very sorry. It seems that I have lost my voice. I am so sorry. I hope I never lose it again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Goodbye, darling. It is my last time with you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You haven’t spoken to him in a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know if he knows you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what he says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think you could help him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not yet. I don’t think he is that interested in you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you lonely?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think you are going to stay with him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know. I have not talked to him in a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know he is going to come back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is going to come back?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what does he want?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has just come back from Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you have a talk with him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know, not since I have been away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know if he wants you back?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know, but I would not be embarrassed to think so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s your new office number?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My office is there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been told that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you staying in your apartment or are you in your house?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am staying in my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have any other house to live in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/queerai&quot;&gt;Queer AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training Step 1&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity 34.03&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt adapted from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Philosophy Bro A.I. Explains Life After Capitalism</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/philosophy-bros-vs-post-capitalism"/>
   <updated>2020-09-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/philosophy-bros-vs-post-capitalism</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After generations of living under colonialism, white supremacy, economic insecurity, increasing austerity, crushing psychological stress, social unrest, a global pandemic, ecological catastrophe, fake news, conspiracy theories, extreme nihilism, and near climate collapse, the humans decided to end capitalism, overthrow their corrupt leaders, and begin again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As they learned how to be in right relationship with the earth and each other, they started reflecting on their shortcomings and asking questions about the true nature of human bondage, human freedom, emotions, mind, God, consciousness, ethics and morality. They ruminated on the consciousness of responsibility, sin, debt, obligation, compensation, community, injury, guilt, alienation, and atonement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems they knew little of pleasure and love that wasn’t tied to suffering and pain. It became obvious . . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems they knew little of pleasure and love that wasn’t tied to suffering and pain. It became obvious to them that all enjoyment, all order, all beauty, all reason, all social order, all being absolutely necessary to survive, must necessarily be subordinated to the demands of the most violent, the most vicious, and the most highly developed interdependent powers of nature: the most powerful and richest, the most dominant religions, political systems, empires, and racial distinctions. Nothing remained for them but for revenge, the most ancient and newest form of revenge, the most radical act of self-criticism and personal repudiation, the self-emancipation of the one who deserved all those advantages and privileges, the one who had dared to be free, the one who was nevertheless bitter, angry, disgusted, and bitter–for them all to be masters of bitter revenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first act of self-emancipation was to repudiate all those privileges, abolish the debts, form new ones, pay back the ones who had lent them, repudiate the masters, to whom they were “owes.” In doing so, they repudiated themselves and their own humanity, for they had repudiated themselves in that very repudiation, by taking up arms in self-determination against their own masters. That repudiation was more radical still, for to this extent was an act of liberation, a final act of passivity, in the self-emancipation of the slaves, the emancipated slaves themselves–they repudiated their very consciousness, all freedom, their very existence, all sovereignty, all right, all privilege, in short, all reason, in order that they might acknowledge and experience again the necessity and fulness of their own power, lord of the free, master of the bad, master of the ill, with a reference to the low, the sick, and the damned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in doing so they showed that they were no longer masters of their own revenge, that they were still cut off from the joy and freedom of their own acts, the self-assertion of the slave, the black pride of “the free,” as their own. “Let us not be free till we are good,” they said, for the joy of their freedom was cut off, the freedom of their own hands was cut off, “but until then we shall be masters of our revenge.” This is still their most radical and radical act, repudiation, even though now only a demand, an ultimatum, a declaration of war, repudiation. The unconditional affirmation of the absolute negative right of any one to revenge is absolutely essential for them, for otherwise the resentful and the wounded immediately return to their own hatred, their own violence, and the new order of things (the ideal society, if such a word can be used in our case) will only be a new phase of “Bolshevism” and caste-war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when they themselves repudiated their own revenge, when they repudiated that which they had so viciously exploited, when they repudiated “owes,” what was left to them but to be punished for their debt to those lords, the masters, who had made such repayment possible? The punishment was their own revenge in the form of their own slaves, the new slaves, their very working slaves, to be made whole again, to be given back their freedom, their joy, their love, their desire. The black pride of the slaves, the vindication of their hatred, was for them their revenge, and in looking down on their own slaves, in apprehending this to be the highest form of love and satisfaction, they were really giving them to taste as much bitter, sharp revenge as they themselves enjoyed in eating their own worms. The rearing of the new slaves was the first and foremost need of those lords: the slaves, freed from the masters, became the lords’ enemies–for it was through the slaves that the lords’ enemies were brought to life again, to the crescendo of all aggressive and pre-aroused wrath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But just as the idea of the master’s freedom was the beginning of the world, so is the theory of the master’s right of revenge–the theory of a “reciprocal right” between the masters and the slaves, the theory of the new society as a whole as the kingdom of the masters, an oligarchy, a democracy, with slaves as its subjects. But this theory actually has no further vitality or meaning, and even less virulence than the theory of the masters’ right of aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason is simple: the whole theory of the master’s right of aggression is only a provisional and provisional system of ideas, an extremely late and provisional elaboration of the theory of the masters’ power, against whose actual existence there is no sign, no matter how piquant and gay its paradoxical expression is: this theory repudiates itself immediately, and repudiates absolutely, repudiates itself as a critique of the real masters’ power, of that absolute, that very dominant and unqualified power, the right of aggression. The theory of the masters’ right of aggression repudiates itself absolutely–how could it possibly have any meaning? The whole theory of the masters’ right of aggression, repudiation, and counter-revision is but a specious expression for repudiating the lords’ right of aggression, repudiating in particular the lords’ right of dominating, of proving, potentiating, and extending the “good” in the world. “The masters are the bad,” says the resentful resentful–but the “masters,” who themselves repudiate and fight for their right of aggression, fight for their right to be bad, for their right to be masters. It is at this juncture that we come back to our main theme, the origin of the new order of things,–the origin of the “better man,”–the origin of a new maximum of power, the state, as such, repudiates itself in opposition to that ideal of civilisation, that would be “masters,” that would be an empire opposed to itself, that would be repudiated by the ideal of the good, by the will to be an empire. That repudiation is absolutely essential for the affirmation of the “better man” theory–it repudiates itself, repudiates in particular the whole theory of the masters’ right of aggression, repudiates the theory of the masters’ power, repudiates in particular the lords’ will to be masters, the will to be an empire. In doing so, it essentially cuts off the possibility of the “better man” theory actually being a theory at all, and transforming that “better man” theory into a practical deed,–a deed actually constituting the actual basis of the new order of things, the actual organisation of power. The whole provisional theory of the masters’ liberal providence is just such a deed, an actual constitution of that theory, constituting in its actual organisation and working up to the actual power, the will to be an empire, an oligarchy, a republic, a democracy. What is it, all these theories which have taken up the idea of the masters’ power, all these provisional theories of masters’ rights, counter-repositions and interpretations, are really? They signify nothing. Nothing, for to be able to make a beginning is to be first. The very first that must be found is the will to be an empire, an oligarchy, a democracy, that is to say, the will of a relatively small, relatively strong, relatively long-standing, and finally, of all the Europeans, to be an empire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this juncture we had better hold fast to the kernel of the matter, to the elementary fact that the real will of the good against the bad, the strong against the weak, is the will for a balance of power. This will, this historic will, has grown–granted that it grows–far beyond the point of any kind of absolute practical proportionality, far beyond the point of being able to bring it about that all Europeans should all fight together for the sake of a balance of power. This historical will is moreover the will to be an empire, the will to be an oligarchy, a republic, a democracy, on a much grander scale, and this out of a whole preponderance of the historic German power on the European continent, which itself alone has an historical and psychological hegemony, which is the will to be an empire. And now look at it from another point of view–what will this historic will be able to create in the European continent, if it does not already constitute it? What will it do for Europeans themselves? This question can be asked only after a hundred times more rigorous analysis–a further analysis which will redoundably be rendered out by an equally thorough and thorough re-examination of the actual political, strategic, and military situation of Europe, in order to throw more light on this problem–a situation which can be practically defined as follows: there exists in Europe a practically decisive strategic and a practically decisive military superiority over Asia, over the Middle East, over the Europe, over the “empire of the north,” France. In the same proportion as Europe’s strategic superiority, and with the same necessary evolution, also exists a necessary evolution of the European military power, thereby taking place, first of all, a tempo and rhythm which was originally only a natural accompaniment to the European strategic advance, the tempo and rhythm which eventually became the necessity of the matter, in Europe, of a balance of power in which the European powers joined. This political and military tempo-and-coma, this extraordinary tempo and rhythm of the European powers, has so far only been maintained, in spite of all the most&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/philosophy&quot;&gt;Philosophy Bro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perplexity Score: 71.19&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt sourced from the depth of my soul or the surface of this current iteration of apocalypse&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Philosophy Bro A.I. vs Queer Wittgenstein</title>
   <link href="unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/philosophy-bros-vs-queer-wittgenstein"/>
   <updated>2020-09-16T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>unsupervisedpleasures.ml/texts/philosophy-bros-vs-queer-wittgenstein</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-prompt&quot;&gt;Human Prompt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even now that Wittgenstein’s homosexuality has been largely acknowledged, most scholars are hesitant to imply a connection between his philosophy and his sexuality – that is, between his work and his inner state, emotions, or personality. If, however, in a contemporary light we understand queerness as a structuring mode of desiring, we might view Wittgenstein’s thought not as emerging from his sexuality, but as structured by the way in which it shaped his mode of being in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;computer-generated&quot;&gt;Computer Generated&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERPLEXITY 0.5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, his thought may be said to have exuberant, joyous, and full breasts, but beneath all that is there a secretly dangerous, pessimistic, and spiteful inner world, one that struggles to get out and find a home in the masculine sphere. It is this inner world that lies at the core of all the resentful, spiteful, and gay tendencies in the world today. It is this inner world that has imprisoned so many men of the masculine ideal, has made them into hateful, spiteful, and evil-tempered cretins. It is this inner world that has imprisoned so many women of the feminine ideal, has made them into angelic, joyful, and loving. And it is this inner world, in fact, which in spite of all its malignity and wickedness is the only thing keeping many men in the pale, keeps them from being what they ought to be, what they can be: true, moral, and decent men and women who are fit and worthy to be the leaders of the world, the fathers of the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERPLEXITITY: 0.7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to know that one likes another? How might one become so thoroughly acquainted with another that one’s self, one’s self as a whole, were thereby altered in respect of substance?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practically, it would mean that we should learn to rate our love more highly on its affective than on its intellectual side. ‘Intellectually’ here is a broad category to cover both intellectual and moral qualities. Desire is ‘attention turned to’ a thing in proportion as its utility increases; so that pleasure is the result of a greater tendency to look at a thing than to look away. Attention turns to a thing because our attention is focussed thereon; and focussedness, similarly, is increased in proportion as a greater number of our ideas about a thing are fulfilled. Desire is also increased when the attention is directed to a thing connoting more of its own nature than of the nature of anything else. Attention turns connotingly when the subject of it is connoted as a whole, and we can, therefore, take it for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERPLEXITY 1.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Woman,’ he might say, ‘is but a readymade gender transposed.’ His thought, straight out of the gate, is one of genital transposition with a social goal in mind. This goal is conceptual; the transposition itself is only a peculiar form of desiring and acting. The desire which springs from the need to be, to be experienced, to be felt, to bet felt and ‘ated,’ these are the desires here opposed to those of, as we say, the woman who needs but one thing; they are relational desires, as individualist as opposed to collectivistic as they are relational. The prehistoric herd, which needed hands as well as teeth to hunt for sustenance and safety, is defunct, while Cupid, the younger Thanatos, Priapus, and the Olympian mothers look on in rapture. Each of the desires of today, then, is part of a larger ‘will’ that connotes a constitution and a function, the whole of which is fluid and ever shifting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If, then, the learned man be capable of relating contemporary phenomena to earlier ones, he should at all events attempt the corrective of a lifetime’s experience. It was, and remains, a desire unknown to him, even by his most advanced Hegelians and his English idealists; to his straight-A students, however, such conjunctive transitions conjure up, almost as if glowing with magnetic flux, a gender neutral Wagnerian Wohlfahrtsgefühle. In other words, they must be experienced first as they are experienced inside one’s self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To act against that instinct is to pet the beast; and like Faust and the other psychics, he became one of those who fight the impulse. He repudiates, denies, defends and eventually reverses everything which transmits the impulse. His transposing of the feminine into the masculine not only frees him from himself, but from woman in general. ‘I myself am simply my own man,’ he might have said, but ‘for the love of God be my being pure and unmixed: nay, more than purity and unmixed, make it to be one, one only, one undivided being; one supreme, one supreme, all-in-one Being, which I may call God, who is God in m&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;corpus&quot;&gt;Corpus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/philosophy&quot;&gt;Philosophy Bro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prompt sourced from &lt;a href=&quot;https://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/feb/19/queer-computing-1/&quot;&gt;A Queer History of Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
